[
    {
      "cell_ids": [
        5
      ],
      "question": "How many ratings are included in this dataset after reading 50% of the rows?",
      "answer": "6445351",
       "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
       "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
    },
     {
      "cell_ids": [
        6
      ],
      "question": "What type of data is stored in the `ratings` DataFrame?",
      "answer": "user_id, artist, track and playlist",
      "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
       "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
     },
    {
      "cell_ids": [
        8
      ],
        "question": "What is the output of the  `create_interaction_matrix` function?",
      "answer": "Pandas dataframe with user-item interactions ready to be fed in a recommendation algorithm",
      "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
          "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
    },
      {
       "cell_ids": [
              13
          ],
        "question": "What is the output of `create_user_dict` function?",
            "answer": "Dictionary type output containing interaction_index as key and user_id as value",
             "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
          "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
      },
      {
          "cell_ids": [
              14
          ],
          "question": "What does `create_item_dict` function return?",
           "answer": "A dictionary type output containing item_id as key and item_name as value.",
           "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
          "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
      },
    {
     "cell_ids": [
              16
          ],
           "question": "What is the use of the `LightFM` class?",
          "answer": "It is used for building a matrix factorization based recommendation model.",
           "task": "Recommendation Systems",
           "skill": "Matrix Factorization"
      },
      {
        "cell_ids": [
              16
          ],
           "question": "What is the meaning of the `n_components` parameter?",
            "answer": "It represents the number of embeddings you want to create to define item and user.",
             "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
          "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
       },
     {
        "cell_ids": [
              16
          ],
           "question": "What type of loss function does the model use by default?",
            "answer": "warp",
              "task": "Basic Data Analysis",
           "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
        },
       {
          "cell_ids": [
              16
          ],
          "question": "What does the `n_jobs` parameter represent in the `runMF` function?",
          "answer": "It represents the number of cores used for execution of the model.",
          "task":"Basic Data Analysis",
          "skill": "Basic Data Analysis"
      },
    {
      "cell_ids": [
              16
          ],
      "question": "What does the `sample_recommendation_user` function returns?",
           "answer": "It returns a list of recommended items for a given user",
          "task": "Recommendation Systems",
           "skill": "Collaborative Filtering"
      }
  ]